<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/code/pfs.css"?><TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>An ordinance of the Lords and Commons assembled in Parliament directing the payment of all duties upon the revenue to be made to the severall receivers appointed or to be appointed.</title>
            <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
         </titleStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 4KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 1 1-bit group-IV TIFF page image.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2016-02">2016-02 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">B22101</idno><idno type="EEBO-CITATION">10268633</idno>
  <idno type="VID">204630</idno>
  <idno type="EEBO-PROQUEST">2240952414</idno>
  
            <idno type="STC">Wing E1838</idno>
            <idno type="OCLC">10268633</idno>
            <availability><p>This keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above is co-owned by the
    institutions providing financial support to the Early English Books Online Text Creation
    Partnership. This text is available for reuse, according to the terms of <ref target="https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/"> Creative Commons 0 1.0 Universal
    licence</ref>. The text can be copied, modified, distributed and performed, even for commercial
    purposes, all without asking permission.</p></availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online text creation partnership.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt><relatedItem type="facs" target="https://data.historicaltexts.jisc.ac.uk/view?pubId=eebo-e"/>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. B22101)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 204630)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1641-1700 ; 1382:25)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>An ordinance of the Lords and Commons assembled in Parliament directing the payment of all duties upon the revenue to be made to the severall receivers appointed or to be appointed.</title>
                  <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>1 broadside.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>Imprinted for Iohn Wright,</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
                  <date>1644.</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>"Die Sabbathi 23 Decemb. 1643."</note>
                  <note>Signed at end: Io. Browne Cler. Parliament.</note>
                  <note>Reproduction of original in the Huntington Library.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,363 texts created during Phase 1 of the project have been released into the public domain as of 1 January 2015. Anyone can now take and use these texts for their own purposes, but we respectfully request that due credit and attribution is given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Full documentation of the original data capture process is available from the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.
   All versions of the texts are now archived and freely available for download. See <ref target="https://textcreationpartnership.org/faq/#faq05">the TCP Download FAQ</ref>
   for detailed information. The TEI P5 versions are also freely available from the <ref target="https://github.com/textcreationpartnership">TCP Github repository</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp" matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)" replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char" matchPattern="(.+)" replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term type="geographic_name">Great Britain --  History --  Civil War, 1642-1649.</term>
               <term type="geographic_name">Great Britain --  Politics and government --  1642-1649.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2014-02 </date>
            <label>Apex CoVantage</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images </change>
         <change>
            <date>2014-05 </date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo </label>Sampled and proofread </change>
         <change>
            <date>2014-05 </date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited </change>
         <change>
            <date>2015-03 </date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion </change>
      <change><date>2021-05 </date><label>lb</label>TEI P5 conversion </change></revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <body>
         <div type="Parliamentary_ordinance">
            <pb facs="tcp:204630:1"/>
            <head>AN ORDINANCE OF THE LORDS and COMMONS Assembled in Parliament, Directing the payment of all duties upon the Revenue to be made to the severall Receivers, appointed, or to be appointed.</head>
            <opener>
               <dateline>
                  <date>Die Sabbathi 23 Decemb. 1643.</date>
               </dateline>
            </opener>
            <p>
               <seg rend="decorInit">W</seg>Hereas diverse Mannors, Lands, Tenements and Hereditaments of Papists, Delin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>quents, and ill affected persons in diverse Counties, Cities, &amp; places within this Realm of <hi>England,</hi> Dominion of <hi>Wales,</hi> and Port and Towne of Barwicke, by Ordinances of Parliament, are, and others hereafter may be sequestred, out of which there are sun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dry Fee-Farme Rents, Farme Rents, and other payments due to his Majesty, the Queen, and Prince: And Whereas the Lords and Common in this present Parlia<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ment Assembled, upon the one and twentieth of September last, passed an Ordinance for the siezing upon, and receiving for the use of His Majesty and the Common-wealth, all His Majesties, the Queene and Princes Revenues, of what nature or quality soever, certaine, or casuall, within the said Realm of <hi>England,</hi> Dominion of <hi>Wales,</hi> and Ports and Town of Barwick, together with all the Arrears thereof, and all debts any way due to His Majesty, the Queen or Prince, And to the end that all distractions and confusions of accounts may be avoyded and prevented, &amp; that there may be kept an ex<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>act and distinct account of all His Majesties, the Queen and Princes Revenues, or summes of Mony which have bin, or shall be leavied or received by Ordinance of this present Parliament, The said Lords and Com<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mons therefore doe declare, and Ordeine, and be it Ordeined by the Authority of the same, That all and eve<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ry the rents, summes of Mony, and other duties any way due to His Majesty, the Queen or Prince, charg<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>able upon or issuing forth of any the Mannors, Lands, Tenements or Hereditaments, that are or shall be sequestred as aforesaid, together with all the Arreares thereof, shall be from time to time paid and delive<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>red to the severall receivers, that are, or shal be thereunto appointed by the said Ordinance of Parliament of the 21 of September last, or the Committee for the Revenue, within the severall Counties, Cities or pla<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ces aforesaid: And the said Lords and Commons doe further Declare, Ordaine, and Command, that all and every the Committees of Sequestrations in the severall Counties, Cities, and places aforesaid, and all Treasurers and Collectors, and all others whom it may concerne, that they give obedience, and con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>forme themselves to this present Ordinance, and out of the moneys raised, or arising of all, every, or any of the said sequestred Mannors, Lands, Tenements, or Hereditaments, they forthwith, and so hereafter from time to time, doe pay the said severall Rents and sums of Money, which are or shal be due out of the same unto His Majesty, the Queen, or Prince, unto the said severall and respective Receivers within the se<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>verall Counties, Cities, and places aforesaid, whose severall and respective Acquittance or Acquitances shall be a sufficiennt discharge to the severall Sequestrators, Treasurers, Collectors, and all others, for such sums of money, as they, or any of them shall pay according to the direction of the Ordinance.</p>
            <closer>
               <signed>Io. Browne Cler. Parliament.</signed>
            </closer>
         </div>
      </body>
      <back>
         <div type="colophon">
            <p>Imprinted at <hi>London</hi> for <hi>Iohn Wright,</hi> and are to be sold at his Shop in the Old Baylie, 1644.</p>
         </div>
      </back>
   </text>
</TEI>